Contact

Dhaka Bangladesh +880 168 5367 806 (Mobile) sajibshahariarrahman@gmail.

www.linkedin.com/in/shahsajib (LinkedIn) shahsajib.me/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Web Development JavaScript React.js

Languages

English (Full Professional)

Shahariar Rahman Sajib

Frontend Developer at Kalpas Innovations Pvt. Ltd. Dhaka

Summary

Hi,

I am shah. I am a FullStack Web Developer. I have more than 2 years of experience in Javascript (ES6), React, Next.js, Redux, Typescript, MongoDB, Mongoose & Node JS. I am passionate about coding, solving problem is my motto.

I am a freelancer working in this field for 1.5 years. I have developed Social Media, Blog, Agency and eCommerer Websites.

I am open to do remote jobs. Thanks for viweing my profile.

Experience

Kalpas Innovations Pvt. Ltd. Frontend Developer January 2022 - Present (4 months) Vidya Nagar, Hubli, Karnataka 580025, India

Full Stack Developer November 2020 - Present (1 year 6 months)

Education

Knowledge Professional Institute FIA, ACCA · (2017)

Chartered University College FIA · (2016 - 2017)

Adamjee Cantonment College

Higher Secondary School Certificate, Buinsess Studies · (2013 - 2015)

B A F Shaheen College Kurmitola · (2008 - 2013)

Nalua Government Primary School · (2007 - 2008)